♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor ♪
["Mr. Tailor" playing]
- ♪ Fix it ♪
- ♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor ♪
♪ Holding the scissors ♪
♪ One cut, and it's settled ♪
[Cita] Don't ever show yourself
to me and Karla again!
PREVIOUSLY
I'll press charges
for what you did to my child!
Rot in jail!
Maybe we were wrong
to try to rebuild this family.
[Audrey] Stay here with Ibyang.
My child and I are going home.
[Atoy] Don't leave. I love you and Janine.
I thought things were okay
with Aunt Audrey.
[Ame] I'm sure Atoy won't leave you.
He'll make a compromise.
Your Brother Emerson is here…
um…
to take you home.
Why are you punishing me?
[Audrey] Your daddy is sending
Ibyang home.
I just feel bad for her.
Don't cry anymore,
because you and Daddy are back together,
and we're complete now.
Then he shouldn't have promised
to adopt Ibyang
if he wasn't going to do it.
[Ibyang] I won't force myself on someone
who can't choose me.
[Atoy] Ibyang left me.
She's upset with me. She's sulking.
Godmother…
Are they here?
[music fades]
Ame!
Come out! [inhales]
It's better if you all face each other.
- [Cita] Go ahead.
- [Ame] Oh.
[melancholic music playing]
Atoy, I'm sorry.
Ibyang doesn't want to see you.
That's why she asked to leave.
She said she'll give way to your family.
Anyway, once I find another job,
I'll leave the shop too.
Hey, what do you mean you're leaving?
Who's leaving?
You still have work with me.
You'll work for me, no one else.
Ame, what's wrong with you?
- Okay. Since you said so.
- [Cita chuckles]
Eh, ah-- Where's Ibyang?
- [soft moan]
- [music fades]
[clatters]
[Ibyang gasps]
[suspicious music playing]
Ibya-- Ibyang!
Ibyang, come here.
Let's talk, Ibyang!
Hey!
[music fades]
Ibyang?
[Atoy] Ibyang.
[Ibyang sighs]
Ibyang, can we talk?
I'm going to sleep!
I'm tired.
- [imitates snoring sound]
- [mellow music playing]
Okay, okay…
I have something for you there…
Come… Come home.
You can rest at the house.
It'll be a waste if you don't get
what I bought for you.
It's your favorite.
Ibyang.
Ibyang, I'm sorry.
- The decision I made hurt me too, but…
- [sniffles]
[Atoy sighs] Please, come back home.
I shouldn't.
[sniffles]
Because… I shouldn't be in your house.
Janine should be the one.
Because she's your real child.
That's why you chose her.
You don't need to explain.
[melancholic music playing]
Okay.
I'll just send
what I got for you through Ame.
But Ibyang, remember this.
I love you.
If you change your mind,
you're always welcome at home.
I'll be there, waiting for you.
All right?
I love you too.
[sniffles]
I just don't want your family
to have problems.
I'm not really your child.
I'm just borrowing you as a father.
[epic music playing]
[crying]
[music fades]
[suave theme music playing]
[motorcycle revving]
[sewing machine whirring]
[scratches]
[snipping]
[sewing machine clacking]
[gunshots]
[clacking]
[clicking]
[snipping]
[music swells]
[electronic blipping]
[music fades]
[birds chirping]
Audrey, dear!
How was your vacation with your daughter?
It was fine, Dad. Janine enjoyed it.
But you… Your smile is different.
- [in English] What?
- [pleasant music playing]
Dad, it's nothing!
[in English] Oh, come on,
Audrey, my child.
[Audrey chuckles softly]
It's impossible that it's nothing.
You're smiling up to your ears.
Ah--
[in English] Dad!
[chuckles]
[in English] Okay, fine.
[in English] The guy
that you heard on the phone…
was Atoy.
[feel-good music playing]
[in English] We've decided to pick up
where we left off.
We agreed to fix our relationship,
since we have a child.
[in English] Okay.
[in English] Why don't you
invite Atoy over
for dinner tonight?
[in English] Are you sure, Dad?
[relieved chuckle]
[in English] Okay.
[in English] Thank you.
- [music fades]
- [Red, in English] See?
[Red smirks]
Crazy, right?
[Red sighs]
[in English] I-Is that Atoy?
[in English] C-Can I see?
[suspicious music playing]
Was he with you on your trip?
[in English] Um, yes.
Daddy Atoy might even join us
here at home again.
Because he and Mommy are back together!
- [titters]
- [Martina smirks]
[in English] Really?
I mean-- I have a bad feeling
he'll just leave your mommy again.
She'll get hurt.
Do you want that?
Mm. Why would he leave Mommy?
They love each other.
[in English] You don't know that.
Isn't your daddy poor?
What if he only came back
because he wants to enjoy our lifestyle?
My daddy isn't that poor.
[Janine inhales] You, Aunt Martina?
Did you marry Uncle Red because he's rich?
[laughing]
Anyway.
I'm just happy our family of three
is complete again.
[Janine chuckles]
[in English] That was good.
[chuckles, inhales]
[in English] This can't happen.
[sighs, in English] Yes.
This is what I was saying.
It's risky if Atoy
becomes part of our family.
You need to convince Dad to say no.
[in English] I know what to tell him.
[tense music playing]
[music fades]
[in English] Oh, yes. Uh… We're doing
something about it.
[in English] Dad.
[in English] I'll call you back.
Thank you.
[in English] Yes.
You need to talk to Audrey.
Tell her it's a bad idea to get
back together with Atoy.
[sinister music playing]
[smirks] Why?
What's wrong with that?
[suspicious music playing]
Atoy is a tracker.
He has many connections.
He might dig up your past businesses.
Your smuggling.
[in English] What do you mean?
That ivory shipment before, remember?
[in English] You told me
everything was going well.
Your men messed it up again!
It failed because of him.
I retaliated, and someone
got dragged into it.
Atoy was there.
There! That's him.
[car engine revving]
[crashes]
[people gasp]
What do you mean?
It doesn't matter anymore.
It's just a bad idea.
Say it now
before I lose patience with you!
[music fades]
I hit-and-run Atoy's father.
- What?
- [tense music playing]
You're reckless as always!
I didn't mean it!
[in English] You're an idiot!
Why are you only telling me this now?
I didn't know
Atoy and Audrey were connected.
It's a bad idea, Dad.
Our family is doomed
if those two end up together.
[intense music playing]
[in English] I will deal with him.
[music swells]
[music fades]
Whoa! Atoy!
Looking sharp.
You're dressed to the nines!
- Ah. Thanks! Do I look good?
- Yes. Wait.
Is this your new mission?
Pretending to be…
a corrupt politician?
Oh, take me with you.
I'll pretend to be your bodyguard.
Like, uh…
[in English] Roger, roger.
- [quirky music playing]
- Ah, Congressman is coming out. Roger.
Congressman is coming out.
I can do it. Take me with you.
No. I'm going to Audrey's.
Yes, and you know them, right?
They're rich.
Of course, I want to look presentable,
even if I'm nervous.
- Wow!
- [Atoy] Huh?
Wow! You're something else.
You're sharper than a needle.
You even managed to find love again?
- [chuckles]
- Huh?
[stutters] Even while doing this, uh…
special super spy,
slash, uh… tailor?
- Oh?
- [Emerson] Wow.
Take me with you.
[clicks tongue] ‘Son…
You know my job is dangerous.
You've seen it.
Sometimes I look for missing roosters.
- [chuckles]
- But most of the time… criminals.
So, even if I want you with me,
it's too dangerous.
So, as much as possible,
don't talk about it.
Make sure no one knows.
That's how it should be, so we're safe.
- Got you!
- Oh my god! Son of a-
- [Kurt gasps]
- [quirky music playing]
[in English] Guys, it's just me,
Brother Kurt!
What are you doing there,
Brother Kurt? Huh?
What's wrong with you?
Have you been there long?
- Who sent you?
- [gasps]
You're a spy, aren't you?
No, no, no!
[in English] I just-- I came by
to give Atoy and Ibyang some pares
'cause you know, I have--
[in English] I had some extra.
And then, you know,
I heard your guys' conversation,
so I didn't come closer.
[in English] But you know, I swear,
I didn't hear you guys talking.
[in English] Okay? I just-- Promise, but…
You know…
Is it true, Atoy,
that you're like a secret killer spy?
[in English] Like… [chuckles] Like…
- "Bond. James Bond."
- [quirky sting]
Or maybe… uh… [stutters]
Who was that? [imitates gun firing sound]
[in English] Uh, John Wick or maybe even…
[imitates grunting sound]
Jackie Chan!
Something like that.
Uh, it's, uh…
[in English] It's actually something
like that, but not something like that.
[in English] None of the above.
[in English] He's simply, uh…
Atoy, aka The Master Cutter.
- [laid-back music playing]
- [grunting and groaning]
[thumping and thudding]
That's why he's good at fighting!
Boom! Whoa!
[in English] But that's why
you have to shut your mouth,
- because nobody knows.
- [gasps]
[in English] Yes, yes, yes.
Of course, of course, of course!
Of course.
But Atoy, you know,
if you need my help at all,
like catering for your missions
or being your assistant,
I'm available. You just say when.
- Hmm.
- [Emerson cackles]
- [in English] Wait a minute.
- [sighs]
[in English] Brother Kurt,
you have to get in line,
because I'm the number two
of Mr. Man over here.
Hmm…
Brother Kurt…
[music fades]
Whatever you heard…
Hmm?
Nothing, nothing.
[in English] That's, uh…
That's top secret. Okay?
[in English] So, I suggest you…
you take it to your grave.
Ay.
[in English] Because, um, I can do things,
I have done things,
you don't want to know.
[rock music playing]
- [in English] Understood?
- [mutters]
Mmm.
[in English] In short, if you spill
the beans, no more pork and beans.
Ah. [titters]
I get it, guys.
[Kurt sighs]
- [in English] Relax, Kurt.
- [Kurt chuckles nervously]
Relax. It's just me.
[Emerson cackling]
[music fades]
Ibyang, eat now!
Hmm, Atoy really knows your favorites.
Come on, eat!
It would be a waste.
[melancholic music playing]
Mmm, let him and his daughter eat that.
[sobs]
He chose Janine anyway.
Let them eat it.
[sobbing]
You don't want it?
I'll eat it then.
Hmm! It's delicious!
This is so delicious!
The sauce is perfect!
Hmm! So, so good!
Hmm!
I might finish it all!
Hmm! Mmm-hmm. Hmm!
So yummy. Atoy is really good!
Hmm.
It really is delicious.
Right? Mmm, dip it more!
Ah, come on!
You're just playing hard to get!
So? Are you and Atoy okay now?
No! Let him be!
We're not okay.
Mmm-hmm.
Eat some more.
Mmm?
[in English] He's almost here, Dad.
[in English] Um, I told Janine
to come down in a bit.
- [Dmitri, in English] All right.
- [in English] Everything is ready.
[tense music playing]
[in English] Wow, wow!
[in English] Everyone
is looking expensive.
[Red, in English] Yes.
[in English] What's the occasion?
[pensive music playing]
Good evening.
For you.
[in English] Thank you.
[in English] Perfect timing.
Janine is coming down too.
Brother Atoy, why are you here?
[Dmitri, in English] I invited him, Gavin.
[music fades]
So, I've heard you and my daughter
are back together.
[in English] Is that right, Atoy?
Yes, sir.
[in English] Let's talk
about it over dinner.
[in English] Take your seats.
Atoy…
Sit here.
- [tense music playing]
- Why? This is my seat, right?
He's the guest.
Sir, just give this seat to your son.
He might throw a tantrum.
You're really provoking me, huh?
[in English] Relax.
- [music fades]
- Don't stress too much. It's just a chair.
[tense music playing]
- Uh, sir, I'll just sit beside Audrey.
- Yes.
Stay there. You might cry otherwise.
- What did you say?
- [Dmitri, in English] That's enough, Red.
[upbeat rock music playing]
Sit down.
[chair scraping]
- [music concludes]
- There!
Oh.
You know, while
I was watching you earlier,
my lips felt like
they were about to explode!
Like they'd bleed.
You know, T-Bak,
go buy some iced water from Eploks.
There's none here.
Huh? No way!
I don't want to go there! It's chaotic!
Earlier, I saw Eploks' mom
being confronted by the real wife!
- [T-Bak] Do you know why?
- [Billy] Why?
Because Eploks' mom is a mistress!
[Putoy] So, Eploks is jinxed.
That's why whenever we buy
iced water there. We always lose.
- Exactly.
- He's the child of a mistress.
[T-Bak] Mmm-mmm.
And I'm allergic to that,
so it's a no for me!
[in English] No, no, no, no!
Do you have a problem
with illegitimate children?!
[tense music playing]
What's your problem?!
My problem is your attitude!
You think you're so high and mighty!
Hey! Why are you angry?
We weren't even talking about you.
[music fades]
[Dmitri] Oh, my granddaughter!
- [Dmitri] Hi!
- [Audrey] Janine.
[Janine, in English] Daddy.
[in English] Daddy is here.
[Dmitri] Atoy, Audrey…
[in English] I appreciate
what you're trying to do.
Family is important.
[in English] It always comes first.
That's really what I want too.
To rebuild the family.
Especially now that Janine is here.
I want to always be present for her.
I wasn't close to my father.
And when we finally reconciled,
he was gone shortly.
[suspicious music playing]
[in English] Really?
[in English] That's… That's so sad.
How did Grandpa die, Daddy?
He was hit-and-run, child.
[Atoy] So, you, be careful
when crossing the street.
[Dmitri] Atoy…
[in English] I'm sorry to hear that.
[in English] Yes, sir.
His death anniversary is coming soon.
Imagine, until now,
I still don't know who ran him over.
We're sitting in front of food,
and we're talking about death?
It's like we're uneducated.
[sighs] Right. Sorry.
- [Audrey] Mmm.
- You're smart, huh.
Your tie is crooked.
[suspicious music playing]
- What's it to you--
- [Dmitri] Red!
[in English] Just fix your tie.
[in English] Fix my tie!
- [tense music playing]
- You're not saying it.
[in English] Atoy, please.
[in English] Shall we?
[in English] Yes.
[music swells]
[music fades]
[Dmitri, in English] Finish him, son!
[multiple gunfire]
[suspicious music playing]
Who taught you?
[in English] Yours truly!
[in English] You wanna try it?
[Red] No need.
What did your father teach you?
To sew.
He was a master cutter, a tailor.
But because of sewing, I was trained well.
A gun is like a needle.
You can't tremble.
It must always be precise.
Because the wrong hole ruins the fabric.
The wrong shot ruins the target.
[suspicious music playing]
A gun is an extension of the hand.
Like a sewing machine,
the hand is the extension of a tailor.
[in English] Firm grip, solid stance.
[gunfire blasting]
- [music swells]
- I didn't know
a tailor could become a shooter.
So, you're not just a tracker.
You're also a marksman.
Just inspired, sir.
And this is what I'll do to the one
who ran over my father.
[gunfire blasting]
[tense music playing]
[music fades]
[electronic blipping]
Just because I treated you well
doesn't mean you're the one
I want for my daughter.
I'm just being nice to you
because you're the father
of my grandchild…
UP NEXT
…and that's all.
Uh, what do you mean, sir?
[in English] Your mission
is just to retrieve information.
What information?
A terrorist group known as Obsidian,
reportedly training now
in the Philippines.
[Mercado] This is a national
security matter, Atoy.
[Atoy, in English] Hello, sir!
I found my brother, Andrei Sokolov.
[Samir, in English] Stop.
[in English] What is your name?
[Kurt] Sokolov.
[in English] Mr. Alexei Sokolov.
♪ One cut, and it's settled ♪
♪ Fix it ♪
Subtitle translation by: Rachel C. Arias